Stand your ground
Mine is a war, thriller film directed by Fabio Guaglione.
After a failed assassination attempt, a soldier
finds himself stranded in the desert.
Exposed to the elements, he must survive the dangers of the desert and battle the
psychological and physical toll of the treacherous conditions.
Mike, played by Armie Hammer.
Jenny, played by Annabelle Wallis.
Tommy Madison, played by Tom Cullen.
Mike's Father, played by Geoff Bell.
Mike's Mother, played by Juliet Aubrey.
Berber, played by Clint Dyer.
Mine is a 2016 psychological thriller war film written and directed by Fabio
Guaglione and Fabio Resinaro, in their feature film directorial debuts.
It stars Armie Hammer as a United States Marine who is walking on an unmapped minefield during a botched mission when one
fateful step makes his heart sink as he hears a click underfoot and tries to remain still until help arrives.
The film was released in the United States on April 7, 2017.
The film explores themes of parent child relationship,
landmine, sandstorm, hallucination, flashback.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.